10-cheapwebhosting.com 2003-12-09

# 10-CheapWebHosting.com - Privacy Policy

**10-CheapWebHosting.com Privacy Policy**

**Cookies**

A "cookie" is information stored on your computer by a web server and used to customize your web service in some way. We use cookie to store the information on which site you came from. We never store any information that can identify you personally. You can choose not to accept cookies and still use the our web site. No additional information is collected about your visit, and we do not record information about individual behavior or use of the site.

**Third-Party Sites or Persons**

Please be aware that other web sites that may be accessed through our site may collect personally identifiable information about you. The information practices of those third-party web sites linked from 10-CheapWebHosting.com are not covered by this privacy statement. If you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return. While we strive to protect your personal information, 10-CheapWebHosting.com cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk. 

Other Websites 10-CheapWebHosting.com contain links to other websites that are not operated by 10-CheapWebHosting.com. 10-CheapWebHosting.com is not responsible for the privacy practices of the websites that it does not operate. All text in conjunction with listings in any of the Specialty Hosting sections are provided by and the intellectual property of each particular web hosting company. 10-CheapWebHosting.com does not specifically endorse, favor, or promote any of the individual web host companies listed on this site. 

**Changes/Updates to this Agreement**

10-CheapWebHosting.com reserves the right to change or amend this agreement at any time. 

**Contact 10-CheapWebHosting.com**

If you would like to contact us for any reason regarding our privacy practices, use the contact information here.
